So the first thing we're going to do is apply some foundation primer.
This is a silicone based product.
Silicone is a breathable barrier for the skin, so it's going to allow oxygen in and out of the follicles, so it will not clog the pores and it also will prevent breakouts.
It's oil free, it will give you some oil absorption throughout the day.
So we're just going to take a little bit right on our fingertips, do some fingertip application.
Just gently apply it all over the surface of the skin.
Basically, what this is doing, is it's smoothing the surface of the skin, it's helping to minimize the appearance of any pores.
It also softens any fine lines or wrinkles, so your makeup won't settle into any crevices.
It also prevents your makeup from absorbing into the skin, so it's going to keep your makeup looking a lot fresher throughout the day.
It's going to keep it on a lot longer for you, keep it looking a lot better, it'll soak up any oily shine, and just basically is going to keep your makeup looking really great all day long.
So that's how you would want to apply a primer, prior to your foundation.